[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common shape of large single-vortex tornadoes?", "correct_answer": "Wedge tornadoes", "incorrect_answers": ["Funnel tornadoes", "Stovepipe tornadoes", "Rope tornadoes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What makes almost 99% of the visible universe?", "correct_answer": "Plasma", "incorrect_answers": ["Nitrogen", "Quasars", "Solids"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Penguins secrete salt from their nostrils.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word broccoli comes from the Italian expression piccoli bracci. What does this mean?", "correct_answer": "Little arms", "incorrect_answers": ["Green meat", "Little trees", "Green curls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Every mammal has teeth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these diseases is caused by the African tsetse fly?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Nagana", "Sleeping sickness", "African trypanosomiasis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the mathematical property used in this addition equation: (57 + 63) + 14 = 57 + (63 + 14)?", "correct_answer": "Associative property", "incorrect_answers": ["Commutative property", "Distributive Property", "Identity Property"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For centuries, the herbs from the genus Mentha, commonly known as mint, have been used to treat this medical problem.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Nasal congestion", "Rashes", "Stomach pain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The only Academy Award Robert Altman won, was the Academy Honorary Award for lifetime achievement. How many times was he nominated for best director?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "7", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These parrots are believed to be the best at imitating sounds and human speech.", "correct_answer": "African Grey Parrot", "incorrect_answers": ["Lory", "Amazon Parrot", "Cockatoo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where  would  you  find The Book of Kells?", "correct_answer": "Next to the Book of Durrow", "incorrect_answers": ["Glasgow, Scotland", "Edinburgh, Scotland", "Next to the Blarney Stone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1970s television sitcom All in the Family, what was the nickname by which Archie called Gloria?", "correct_answer": "Little Girl", "incorrect_answers": ["Meathead", "Dingbat", "Pinko"]}]